Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5031 A&B
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.93-E, 1966 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 5)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.93-W, 1967 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 6)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.94-E, 1966 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 7)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.94-W, 1967 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 8)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.95-E, 1967 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 9)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.95-W, 1967 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 10)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.96-W, 1967 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 11)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 96-E, 1966 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 12)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.97-E, 1966 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 13)
- Award No. 97-L-W S.W. No. 2268 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 14)
- Award No. 98-L-E (Box 13-15(B), Folder 15)
- Award No.98-L-W S.W. No. 2276 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 16)
- Award No.99-L-E (Box 13-15(B), Folder 17)
- Award No.99-L-W S.D. 2315 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 18)
- Award No.100-L-E (Box 13-15(B), Folder 19)
- Award No.100-L-W S.D. 2324, SBA No. 589 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 20)
- Award No.101-L-W S.D.2340 SBA No.589 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 21)
- Award No.101-L-E (Box 13-15(B), Folder 22)
- Award No.102-L-W S.D.2424 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 23)
- Award No.102-L-E, TD-618 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 24)
- Award No.103-L-W Docket No.701 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 25)
- Award No.103-L-E, TD-628 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 26)
- Award No.104, S.D. T.D. 724 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 27)
- Award No. 104-L-E, TD, 650 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 28)
- Award No.105-L-W Docket No. 2572 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 29)
- Award No.106-L-W Case S-716 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 30)
- Award No.105-L-E, TD 658 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 31)
- Award No.106-L-E, TD 732 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 32)
- Award No.107-L-W, Docket No.2494 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 33)
- Award No.107-L-E, TD 735 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 34)
- Award No.108-L-W, TD 612 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 35)
- Award No.108-L-E, TD 740 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 36)
- Award No.109-L-E, SD 2285 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 37)
- Award No.109-L-W, TD 629 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 38)
- Award No.110-L-E, System Docket 2320 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 39)
- Award No.110-L-W, TD 651 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 40)
- Award No.111-L-E, SD.2332 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 41)
- Award No.111-L-E, TD.677 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 42)
- Award No.112-L-E, SD.2361 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 43)
- Award No.112-L-W, TD.680 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 44)
- Award No.113-L-E, SD.2363 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 45)
- Award No.113-L-W, TD.692 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 46)
- Award No.114-L-E, SD.2371 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 47)
- Award No.114-L-W, TD.698 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 48)
- Award No.115-L-E, SD.2377 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 49)
- Award No.115-L-W, TD.716 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 50)
- Award No.116-L-E, SD.2384 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 51)
- Award No.116-L-W, TD.726 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 52)
- Award No.117-L-W, SD. S-718 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 53)
- Award No.117-L-E, SD.2402 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 54)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 589. Arbitrations and Awards between Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and Penn Central Company East Region. Years: 1968-1969. Special Board of Adjustment No. 752. Disputes between Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamsh (Box 16-18(B))
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 118-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 1)
    Docket No. 2404
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 120-E, 1968-1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 2)
    Docket No. 2432. Includes: Train maps
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 121-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 3)
    Docket No. 2459
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 122-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 4)
    Docket No. 2460
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 123-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 5)
    Docket No. 2467. Includes: Special Board of Adjustment Nos. 686, 387,361
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 124-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 6)
    Docket No. 2468
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 125-E, 1968-1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 7)
    Docket No. 2469
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 126-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 8)
    Docket No. 2470
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 127-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 9)
    Docket No. 2489
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 128-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 10)
    Docket No. 2512
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 129-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 11)
    Docket No. 2513
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 130-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 12)
    Docket No. 2514
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 131 -E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 13)
    Docket No. 2515
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 132-E, 1968-1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 14)
    Docket No. 2516
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 133-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 15)
    Docket No. 2541
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 134-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 16)
    Docket No. 2553
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 135-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 17)
    Docket No. 2563
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 136-E, 1968-1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 18)
    Docket No. 2564
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 137-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 19)
    Docket No.. 2566
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 138-E, 1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 20)
    Docket No. 2569
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 139-E-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 21)
    Docket No. 2579
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 140-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 22)
    Docket No.2590
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 141-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 23)
    Docket No. TD-669
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 142-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 24)
    Docket No. TD-747
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 143-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 25)
    Docket No. TD-762
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 144-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 26)
    Docket No. TD-764
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 154-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 27)
    Docket No. TD-765
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 146-E, 1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 28)
    Docket No. TD-766
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No. 147-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 29)
    Docket No. TD-767
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 147-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 30)
    Docket No. TD-783
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 149-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 31)
    Docket No. TD-789
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 150-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 32)
    Docket No. TD-789. Includes: Notice of trial or investigation
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 151-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 33)
    Docket No. TD-802
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 152-E, 1968 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 34)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 1, 1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 35)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 2, 1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 36)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 3, 1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 37)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 4, 1969 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 38)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 5, 1970 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 39)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 6, 1970 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 40)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 10, 1970 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 41)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 11, 1970 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 42)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 Award No. 12, 1970 (Box 16-18(B), Folder 43)
- Arbitration cases between Brotherhood of Railroad and Railroad Companies. Special Board of Adjustment No. 752 and 589. (Box 19-20(B))
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.752 Case 13, 1960 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 1)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.752 Case 13-15, 1969-1970 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 2)
    Includes: telegram
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.752 Case 16-18, 1970 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 3)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.752 Case 18-20, 1970 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 4)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.752 Case 20-21, 1970 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 5)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.752 Case 22-23, 1969-1970 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 6)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.752 Case 23-24, 1969-1970 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 7)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No. 1-41, 1966 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 8)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No. 43-86, 1965-1967 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 9)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No. 87-152, 1966-1969 (Box 19-20(B), Folder 10)